

[Muhammad Yusuf Nashirulhaq]

Bandung, West Java, 40295 | +62 822 6059 4898 | piksi.yusuf.18402081@gmail.com https://linktr.ee/myusufn12 /

About Me

I am Muhammad Yusuf Nashirulhaq, the Best Graduate of Information Systems Management at Piksi Ganesha Polytechnic. Have experience in Internship and Work at the Central Bureau of Statistics Bandung City. I have a career interest as an administrative staff, web design and proficient in using Microsoft Office Tools, and IT Support.

Abilities & ompetencies

- **→** HTML
- → Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
- → JavaScript Beginner
- **→** Bootstrap

- **→** PHP Beginners
- **→** Microsoft Office Tools
- → Installing Windows dan Software

Work Experience

Central Bureau of Statistics Bandung (Bandung, Indonesia)

Web Development Internship (October 2021 – January 2022)

- Create a Website Application for the Central Bureau of Statistics Bandung
- Responsible for creating animations on the Upload, Delete, Update pages

Specialty: JavaScript · Front-End Development · HTML · Bootstrap · Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)

Central Bureau of Statistics Bandung (Bandung, Indonesia)

REGSOSEK Dispatcher (November 2022 – March 2023)

- Processing REGSOSEK (Social and Economic Registration) 2022 data
- Communication with the Person in Charge of each sub-district about incomplete field data.
- Fix document errors with the supervisor's knowledge
- Field data anomaly checking

Skills: Details · Communication · Data Entry · Statistical Reporting · Teamwork · Census

Education

D4 Piksi Ganesha Polytechnic (September 2018 - December 2022)

Information Systems Management – GPA 3.66.

SMA PGII 2 Bandung (2015-2018)

Department of Science

- Participated in Student Council Organization Activities (2015-2017).
- Become Head of Public Relations at Student Council.